<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Blog by Robin Cottiss]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blog by Robin Cottiss]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 05:01:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Tableau's Oldest Script Kiddie]]></title><description><![CDATA[Where I test out a new way of introducing myself]]></description><link>https://blog.iseevizz.es//posts/tableaus-oldest-script-kiddie/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.iseevizz.es//posts/tableaus-oldest-script-kiddie/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I tell people I am Tableau’s oldest Script Kiddie. I have a degree in Software Engineering but I have never been a professional developer or programmer. I am not saying I create scripts to attack computer systems or deface websites. What I am saying is that I am unskilled in virtually all the technical skills required of a modern developer. But I can copy/paste code like a Pro. I have copy/pasted in many popular languages like Python, Javascript and SQL. Some languages I have copy/pasted are not so popular or gone forever - MDX, Occam, Pascal, DBase. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I learned the term &lt;em&gt;Script Kiddie&lt;/em&gt; something resonated. I think I liked the &lt;em&gt;Kiddie&lt;/em&gt; part. I have never wanted to me a manager or a CEO. I love being an ‘individial contributer’ I love learning. I am perpetually curious and in awe of nearly everything. Learning is one of my strengths. I learn by doing, trying, questioning and arguing (often arguing with myself). I learn by asking questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scipt Kiddies are usually teenagers but I realised that my approach to learning and my curiosity and excitment about things are the traits of a four year old. Maybe that’s why I have never felt comfortable as a manager. Would you let a four year old manage a team, or run a company? Most of of my past managers had the good sense not to let me manage. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I had an epiphany to other day. This is one advantage of being like a four year old - you have epiphanies all the time! I realised that Tableau was founded by a bunch of four year olds and Tableau has more four year olds than any other company I have ever worked in. How Cool is That!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am proud to be Tableau’s oldest four year old. Maybe that is how I will introduce myself in the future:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello, my name is Robin - I am Tableau’s oldest four year old.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mermaid Test]]></title><description><![CDATA[Test of Markdown graph plugin]]></description><link>https://blog.iseevizz.es//posts/mermaid-test/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.iseevizz.es//posts/mermaid-test/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/konsumer/gatsby-remark-graph&quot;&gt;gatsby-remark-graph&lt;/a&gt; is a plugin to allow &lt;a href=&quot;https://mermaidjs.github.io/&quot;&gt;MermaidJS&lt;/a&gt; diagrams in Markdown code blocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-none&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;```mermaid
graph LR
    A[Square Rect] -- Link text --&gt; B((Circle))
    A --&gt; C(Round Rect)
    B --&gt; D{Rhombus}
    C --&gt; D
```&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;generates this diagram:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;mermaid&quot;&gt;graph LR
    A[Square Rect] -- Link text --&gt; B((Circle))
    A --&gt; C(Round Rect)
    B --&gt; D{Rhombus}
    C --&gt; D&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot;&gt;
      &lt;pre class=&quot;language-none&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;``` mermaid
graph LR
     RD[Raw Data] --&gt; RS[Raw Storage]
     RS[Raw Storage] --&gt; P[Process]
     P[Process] --&gt; CS[Clean Storage]
     CS[Clean Storage] --&gt; Q[Query]
     Q[Query] --&gt; I[Insight]
```&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;will give you this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;mermaid&quot;&gt;graph LR
     RD[fa:fa-spinner Raw Data] --&gt; RS[Raw Storage]
     RS[Raw Storage] --&gt; P[Process]
     P[Process] --&gt; CS[Clean Storage]
     CS[Clean Storage] --&gt; Q[Query]
     Q[Query] --&gt; I[Insight]&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>